<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>goodboyjojo</title>
  <link>https://www.goodboyjojo.com/</link>
  <description>my website</description>
  
   <item>
    <title>talkin bout rss</title>
    <link>https://goodboyjojo.com/blog/posts/rss.html</link>
    <description>
		hello everybody, today im going to talk about rss and recommend a couple good rss feed readers for you to try out.
		RSS (Really Simple Syndication) is a great tool for staying up-to-date with your favorite websites,blogs and other 
		things.It allows you to subscribe to a website's content and receive updates whenever new content is published.
		This saves you time and effort, as you no longer have to manually check websites for new content.If you're looking 
		for a great RSS reader, I highly recommend two options: Newboat and Feedbro.
		
		Newboat is an easy-to-use, cli minimalist reader that makes it simple to keep track of your subscriptions. With its 
		clean interface, you can quickly see what's new, and you can categorize your subscriptions to make it easy to find 
		the content you're interested in. Feedbro is another great option, offering a more feature-rich experience. It allows 
		you to organize your subscriptions into folders, add tags for easy searching, and even includes a built-in web browser 
		for reading articles. as you can see rss is a great way to organize things you look at on the internet and plenty of
		rss feed readers to fit your needs.
    </description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>small rant about the current internet</title>
    <link>https://goodboyjojo.com/blog/posts/dreamcast.html</link>
    <description>
		the internet seems to be boring now due to being controled by big tech corporations and being steralized killing off the individualism and wonder 
		of what the world wide web once was. It used to be fun surfing the internet not knowing where the next link would bring you and enjoying seeing new 
		things and interesting communities instead of the same handfull of sites that everyone goes to now.The cheezy hand-crafted websites were fun to look at 
		seeing the creativity and learning about the person who created it.Now the culture of the internet has changed from personal websites for fun to social media sites 
		that have skinner-box like mechanics to control how users interact with each other and how they consume ideas in general. i miss the old internet and wish it would come back. 
    </description>
  </item>
  
    <item> 
       <title>sega dreamcast for christmas</title>
       <link>https://goodboyjojo.com/blog/posts/internet.html</link>
       <description>
		   hello everybody i got an sega dreamcast for christmas from my mom. I always wanted one out of the nostalgia for when i had one when i was little 
		   and used to play it all the time with my brother. i remember playing sonic adventure and powerstone alot when i was little. to me the dreamcast 
		   is one of the most underrated game consoles of all time. it had a decent libary of games and was the first game console to have online multiplayer 
		   gaming. i was sad when my mom sold my dreamcast for money when i was little but she bought me one for christmas so its ok and all forgiven. in conclusion 
		   got me a sega dreamcast for christmas and spent some time with the fam. 
       </description>
    </item>
  
</channel>

</rss>
